<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PestControlAp</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter Name</string>
    <string name="enter_gender">enter_gender</string>
    <string name="enter_houseno">enter_houseno</string>
    <string name="enter_phone">enter_phone</string>
    <string name="go_back">go back</string>
    <string name="enter_full_names">enter_full_names</string>
    <string name="enter_email">enter_email</string>
    <string name="enter_visit_date">enter_email</string>
    <string name="Choose_from_Moday_Friday">enter_email</string>
    <string name="enter_Pest_to_control">enter_Pest_to_control</string>
    <string name="selection">selection</string>
    <string name="MainActivity">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="SecondActivity">SecondActivity</string>
    <string name="AdvertActivity">AdvertActivity</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="mainactivity">mainactivity</string>
    <string name="secondactivity">secondactivity</string>

    <string name="PestControlSystem">PestControlSystem</string>
    <string name="www_kpest">www_kpest</string>
    <string name="enter">enter</string>
    <string name="for_a_better_quality_deliver">for a better quality deliver</string>
    <string name="they_deal_with_pest_control_on_the_following_rats_cockroaches_and_pet_pest_apart_from_pest_control_they_also_offer_cleaning_services">They deal with pest control on the following rats, cockroaches and pet pest. Apart from pest control they also offer cleaning services.</string>
    <string name="for_a_better_quality_delivery">for_a_better_quality_delivery</string>
    <string name="advert1">Advert</string>
    <string name="form">Form!</string>
    <string name="SearchMore">SearchMore!</string>

    <string name="advertt">Advert</string>
    <string name="appnavigations">AppNavigations</string>
    <string name="we_are_the_best_choice_in_pest_control_as_we_have_advanced_and_smarter_solutions_which_are_eco_friendly_for_the_health_of_our_future_we_use_an_ipm_integrated_pest_management_approach_which_is_more_effective_and_environmentally_sensitive_this_involves_taking_advantage_of_all_appropriate_pest_management_strategies_including_pest_prevention_utilizing_green_methods_and_the_judicious_use_of_pesticides_with_low_to_no_toxicity_ipm_is_not_a_single_pest_control_method_but_rather_involves_integrating_multiple_control_methods_which_are_knowledge_based_and_use_cutting_edge_technologies">We are the best choice in pest control as we have advanced and smarter solutions which are eco-friendly. For the health of our future, we use an IPM (Integrated Pest Management) approach which is more effective and environmentally sensitive. This involves taking advantage of all appropriate pest management strategies, including pest prevention, utilizing green methods and the judicious use of pesticides with low-to-no-toxicity. IPM is not a single pest control method but rather involves integrating multiple control methods which are knowledge based and use cutting edge technologies.</string>
    <string name="modesearch">modesearch</string>
    <string name="Search">Search</string>
    <string name="required_details">required details</string>
    <string name="submition_received">submition received!</string>
    <string-array name="pest">
        <item>Rats</item>
        <item>Coackroaches</item>
        <item>Ticks</item>
        <item>Rodents</item>
        <item>Wiverbirds</item>
        <item>Vulture</item>
        <item>WoodPecker</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="PestControlSystem">
        <item>phone contact: 0741998165</item>
        <item>Email:mwaikings4@gmail.com</item>
        val languages = resources.getStringArray(R.array.Languages)
    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="our_services">Our Services</string>
    <string name="topservices">Topservices</string>
    <string name="view">view</string>
    <string name="Home">Home</string>
    <string name="vist_date">vist_date</string>
    <string name="Required_Details">Required_Details</string>
    <string name="ticks">ticks</string>
    <string name="ReachUs">ReachUs</string>
    <string name="people_of_any_age_with_asthma_or_other_chronic_diseases_may_be_more_likely_than_healthy_individuals_to_get_sick_after_pesticide_exposure_some_individuals_are_also_more_sensitive_to_the_odor_or_other_irritant_effects_of_certain_pesticides_but_no_matter_what_their_individual_sensitivities_people_in_the_greatest_danger_of_pesticide_illness_are_those_whose_exposure_is_highest_such_as_workers_who_mix_or_apply_pesticides_people_who_use_pesticides_in_their_homes_may_also_be_overexposed_and_become_ill_especially_if_they_do_not_carefully_follow_the_directions_on_the_product_label_people_living_near_agricultural_fields_are_more_likely_than_urban_residents_to_be_exposed_to_farm_chemicals_although_their_exposure_may_not_necessarily_be_high_enough_to_cause_harmful_effects_what_can_you_do_to_minimize_pesticide_exposure_1_buy_organic_and_locally_grown_fruit_and_vegetables_buying_organic_in_season_produce_from_your_local_market_is_the_best_assurance_of_pesticide_free_produce_to_identify_fruit_grown_organically_look_at_the_little_sticker_the_number_should_be_five_digits_and_start_with_9_e_g_94223_if_you_are_on_a_limited_budget_look_for_organic_choices_for_the_produce_your_family_eats_the_most_national_surveys_have_also_shown_that_fruits_and_vegetables_from_farmers_markets_contain_less_pesticides_even_if_they_re_not_organic_2_wash_fruits_and_vegetables_before_eating_commercial_vegetable_and_fruit_washes_are_available_which_are_formulated_to_remove_chemical_residue_from_produce_examples_are_environn_and_vitanet_available_online_or_at_your_local_health_food_stores_and_some_supermarkets_you_can_also_make_your_own_produce_wash_using_a_very_diluted_solution_of_mild_dish_washing_detergent_1_tsp_detergent_per_gallon_or_4_liters_water_for_grapes_strawberries_green_beans_and_leafy_vegetables_swirl_the_foods_in_a_dilute_solution_of_dish_detergent_and_water_at_room_temperature_for_5_to_10_seconds_then_rinse_with_slightly_warm_water_for_other_fruits_and_vegetables_use_a_soft_brush_to_scrub_the_food_with_the_solution_for_about_5_to_10_seconds_then_rinse_with_slightly_warm_water_3_know_which_fruits_and_vegetables_have_higher_levels_of_pesticide_residue_much_of_the_health_risks_associated_with_pesticide_residues_on_produce_are_concentrated_in_a_relatively_small_number_of_fruits_and_vegetables_by_knowing_which_fruits_and_vegetables_pose_the_highest_risks_you_can_take_adequate_precaution_such_as_washing_the_food_more_carefully_peeling_the_skin_on_some_fruit_or_avoiding_commercial_sources_to_learn_which_foods_have_higher_pesticide_residues_see_our_page_pesticides_and_produce_4_grow_your_own_produce_a_backyard_garden_plot_as_small_as_400_sq_ft_can_provide_much_of_the_required_produce_for_a_family_of_four_organic_methods_can_replace_the_need_for_pesticides_and_chemical_fertilizers_and_tending_the_garden_is_a_healthy_activity_for_children_planting_perennial_crops_like_asparagus_blueberries_and_strawberries_will_provide_crops_for_years_with_very_little_work_even_homegrown_produce_should_be_washed_before_eating_however_since_pesticides_are_sprayed_aerially_in_some_regions_of_the_country_and_other_wind_blown_contaminants_may_reach_your_garden_to_learn_more_see_our_pages_on_backyard_vegetable_gardening_natural_garden_pest_control_5_use_non_toxic_methods_for_controlling_insects_in_the_home_and_garden_using_chemical_based_commercial_insect_pest_control_treatments_may_introduce_chemicals_to_your_home_which_pose_more_of_a_threat_than_the_insects_they_are_designed_to_kill_epa_spokesman_dale_kemery_recommends_that_parents_try_other_pest_control_tactics_before_resorting_to_pesticide_use_in_the_home_or_garden_there_are_effective_non_toxic_methods_for_controlling_insect_problems_in_the_home_such_as_diatomaceous_earth_which_will_kill_a_broad_range_of_common_indoor_insects_without_posing_any_hazard_to_your_family_or_pets_to_learn_more_about_safe_methods_for_controlling_insect_pests_see_our_page_on_natural_insect_pest_control_in_the_garden_growing_healthy_plants_using_organic_methods_is_the_best_pest_deterrent_and_there_are_a_variety_of_natural_pest_control_methods_such_as_beneficial_insects_non_toxic_remedies_traps_and_barriers_to_learn_more_see_our_page_natural_garden_pest_control_6_have_a_no_shoes_policy_in_your_home_when_visitors_to_your_home_walk_across_a_lawn_that_has_been_treated_with_chemical_fertilizers_and_herbicides_residue_from_these_chemicals_may_be_tracked_into_your_home_in_some_instances_these_residues_may_last_for_years_in_carpeting_and_on_floor_surfaces_the_simple_practice_of_leaving_shoes_at_the_door_will_minimize_this_risk_and_reduce_your_home_cleaning_chores_you_can_provide_inexpensive_house_slippers_for_guests_who_are_unused_to_going_shoeless_indoors">People of any age with asthma or other chronic diseases may be more likely than healthy individuals to get sick after pesticide exposure. Some individuals are also more sensitive to the odor or other irritant effects of certain pesticides. But no matter what their individual sensitivities, people in the greatest danger of pesticide illness are those whose exposure is highest, such as workers who mix or apply pesticides. People who use pesticides in their homes may also be overexposed and become ill, especially if they do not carefully follow the directions on the product label. People living near agricultural fields are more likely than urban residents to be exposed to farm chemicals (although their exposure may not necessarily be high enough to cause harmful effects). What can you do to minimize pesticide exposure? 1. Buy organic and locally grown fruit and vegetables. Buying organic, in-season produce from your local market is the best assurance of pesticide-free produce. To identify fruit grown organically, look at the little sticker – the number should be five digits and start with “9” (e.g. 94223). If you are on a limited budget, look for organic choices for the produce your family eats the most. National surveys have also shown that fruits and vegetables from farmers’ markets contain less pesticides even if they’re not organic. 2. Wash fruits and vegetables before eating. Commercial vegetable and fruit washes are available which are formulated to remove chemical residue from produce. Examples are Environné and Vitanet, available online or at your local health food stores and some supermarkets. You can also make your own produce wash using a very diluted solution of mild dish-washing detergent (1 tsp detergent per gallon, or 4 liters, water). For grapes, strawberries, green beans, and leafy vegetables, swirl the foods in a dilute solution of dish detergent and water at room temperature for 5 to 10 seconds, then rinse with slightly warm water. For other fruits and vegetables, use a soft brush to scrub the food with the solution for about 5 to 10 seconds, then rinse with slightly warm water. 3. Know which fruits and vegetables have higher levels of pesticide residue. Much of the health risks associated with pesticide residues on produce are concentrated in a relatively small number of fruits and vegetables. By knowing which fruits and vegetables pose the highest risks, you can take adequate precaution, such as washing the food more carefully, peeling the skin on some fruit, or avoiding commercial sources. To learn which foods have higher pesticide residues, see our page Pesticides and Produce. 4. Grow your own produce. A backyard garden plot as small as 400 sq. ft. can provide much of the required produce for a family of four. Organic methods can replace the need for pesticides and chemical fertilizers, and tending the garden is a healthy activity for children. Planting perennial crops like asparagus, blueberries and strawberries will provide crops for years with very little work. Even homegrown produce should be washed before eating, however, since pesticides are sprayed aerially in some regions of the country, and other wind-blown contaminants may reach your garden. To learn more, see our pages on Backyard Vegetable Gardening, Natural Garden Pest Control. 5. Use non-toxic methods for controlling insects in the home and garden. Using chemical-based commercial insect pest control treatments may introduce chemicals to your home which pose more of a threat than the insects they are designed to kill. EPA spokesman Dale Kemery recommends that parents try other pest-control tactics before resorting to pesticide use in the home or garden. There are effective, non-toxic methods for controlling insect problems in the home such as diatomaceous earth, which will kill a broad range of common indoor insects without posing any hazard to your family or pets. To learn more about safe methods for controlling insect pests, see our page on Natural Insect Pest Control. In the garden, growing healthy plants using organic methods is the best pest deterrent, and there are a variety of natural pest control methods such as beneficial insects, non-toxic remedies, traps and barriers. To learn more, see our page Natural Garden Pest Control. 6. Have a ‘no shoes’ policy in your home. When visitors to your home walk across a lawn that has been treated with chemical fertilizers and herbicides, residue from these chemicals may be tracked into your home. In some instances, these residues may last for years in carpeting and on floor surfaces. The simple practice of leaving shoes at the door will minimize this risk and reduce your home cleaning chores. You can provide inexpensive house slippers for guests who are unused to going shoeless indoors.</string>
    <string name="search">search</string>
    <string name="when_necessary_insecticides_can_help_suppress_housefly_populations_fly_baits_such_as_quickbayt_and_golden_malrin_are_usually_sugar_based_and_contain_a_compound_that_attracts_the_adult_flies_flies_that_feed_on_these_baits_are_killed_by_the_insecticide_they_digest_many_spray_pyrethroid_based_insecticides_can_suppress_houseflies_in_and_around_homes_these_products_can_be_purchased_at_grocery_and_hardware_stores_be_sure_to_read_and_follow_the_instructions_on_all_insecticide_labels_the_information_given_herein_is_for_educational_purposes_only_reference_to_commercial_products_or_trade_names_is_made_with_the_understanding_that_no_discrimination_is_intended_and_no_endorsement_by_the_texas_a_m_agrilife_extension_service_is_implied_search_this_website_free_updates_featured_sections_winter_storm_resources_flu_resources_button_disaster_preparedness_resources_button_disaster_recovery_resources_rss_coronavirus_news_texas_a_and_m_researchers_leaders_in_study_of_covid_19_blocking_enzyme_april_12_2021_texas_aand_m_research_uncovers_first_known_covid_19_uk_variant_in_animals_march_16_2021_texas_a_andm_agrilife_s_top_stories_for_2020_january_18_2021_bat_week_an_opportunity_to_separate_fears_from_facts_october_29_2020_lecture_series_addresses_security_issues_surrounding_food_markets_october_1_2020_stopping_sars_cov_2_along_the_farm_to_plate_supply_chain_september_23_2020_texas_aand_m_coordinated_study_expects_covid_19_economic_impacts_of_2_5_trillion_loss_in_goods_services_nationwide_september_8_2020_west_nile_on_the_rise_in_dallas_tarrant_counties_august_10_2020_covid_19_can_affect_pets_july_27_2020_better_coordination_greater_investment_in_nutrition_research_needed_at_federal_level_july_20_2020"><![CDATA[When necessary, insecticides can help suppress housefly populations. Fly baits, such as QuickBayt® and Golden Malrin®, are usually sugar-based and contain a compound that attracts the adult flies. Flies that feed on these baits are killed by the insecticide they digest. Many spray pyrethroid-based insecticides can suppress houseflies in and around homes. These products can be purchased at grocery and hardware stores. Be sure to read and follow the instructions on all insecticide labels. The information given herein is for educational purposes only. Reference to commercial products or trade names is made with the understanding that no discrimination is intended and no endorsement by the Texas A&M AgriLife Extension Service is implied. SEARCH THIS WEBSITE FREE UPDATES FEATURED SECTIONS Winter Storm Resources Flu Resources button-disaster-preparedness-resources button-disaster-recovery-resources RSS CORONAVIRUS NEWS Texas A and M researchers leaders in study of COVID-19 blocking enzyme April 12, 2021 Texas Aand M research uncovers first known COVID-19 UK variant in animals March 16, 2021 Texas A andM AgriLife’s top stories for 2020 January 18, 2021 Bat Week an opportunity to separate fears from facts October 29, 2020 Lecture series addresses security issues surrounding food, markets October 1, 2020 Stopping SARS-CoV-2 along the farm-to-plate supply chain September 23, 2020 Texas Aand M-coordinated study expects COVID-19 economic impacts of $2.5 trillion loss in goods, services nationwide September 8, 2020 West Nile on the rise in Dallas, Tarrant counties August 10, 2020 COVID-19 can affect pets July 27, 2020 Better coordination, greater investment in nutrition research needed at federal level July 20, 2020]]></string>


</resources>